SAIIY:
Good morning.
Thanks for coming in to see us here at the agency, JOE.
I'm one of the agency representatives,
and my name's SALLY Baker.
JOE:
Hi SALLY.
I think we spoke on the phone, didn't we?
SALLY:
That's right, we did.
So thank you for sending in your CV.
We've had quite a careful look at it and I think we have two
jobs that might be suitable for you.
JOE:
OK.
SALLY:
The first one is in a company based in North London.
They're looking for an administrative assistant.
JOE:
OK.
What sort of company is it?
SALLY:
They're called Home Solutions and they design and make furniture.
JOE:
Oh, I don't know much about that,
but it sounds interesting.
SALLY:
Yes, well as I said, they want someone in their office,
and looking at your past experience it does look as if you fit quite
a few of the requirements.
So on your CV it appears you've done some data entry?
JOE:
Yes.
SALLY:
So that's one skill they want.
Then they expect the person they appoint to attend meetings and take notes there …
JOE:
OK.
I've done that before, yes.
SALLY:
And you'd need to be able to cope with general admin.
JOE:
Filing,
and keeping records and so on?
That should be OK.
And in my last job I also had to manage the diary.
SALLY:
Excellent.
That's something they want here too.
I'd suggest you add it to your CV –
I don't think you mentioned that, did you?
JOE:
No.
SALLY:
So as far as the requirements go, they want good computer skills, of course,
and they particularly mention spreadsheets.
JOE:
That should be fine.
SALLY:
And interpersonal skills – which would be something they'd check with your references.
JOE:
I think that should be OK, yes.
SALLY:
Then they mention that they want someone who is careful
and takes care with details – just looking at your CV, I'd say you're
probably alright there.
JOE:
I think so, yes.
Do they want any special experience?
SALLY:
I think they wanted some experience of teleconferencing.
JOE:
I've got three years' experience of that.
SALLY:
Let's see, yes, good.
In fact they're only asking for at least one year,
so that's great.
So is that something that might interest you?
JOE:
It is, yes.
The only thing is, you said they were in North London
so it would be quite a long commute for me.
SALLY:
OK.
So the second position might suit you better as far as the location goes;
that's for a warehouse assistant and that's in South London.
JOE:
Yes,
that would be a lot closer.
SALLY:
And you've worked in a warehouse before, haven't you?
JOE:
Yes.
SALLY:
So as far as the responsibilities for this position go, they want someone who
can manage the stock, obviously,
and also deliveries.
JOE:
That should be OK.
You've got to keep track of stuff,
but I've always been quite good with numbers.
SALLY:
Good.
that's their first requirement.
And they want someone who's computer literate,
which we know you are.
JOE:
Sure.
SALLY:
Then they mention organisational skills.
They want someone who's well organised.
JOE:
Yes, I think I am.
SALLY:
And tidy?
JOE:
Yes, they go together really, don't they?
SALLY:
Sure.
Then the usual stuff;
they want someone who can communicate well both orally and in writing.
JOE:
OK.
And for the last warehouse job I had, one of the things I enjoyed
most was being part of a team.
I found that was really essential for the job.
SALLY:
Excellent.
Yes, they do mention that they want someone who's used to that, yes.
Now when you were working in a warehouse last time, what sorts of items
were you dealing with?
JOE:
It was mostly bathroom and kitchen equipment, sinks and stoves and fridges.
SALLY:
So you're OK moving heavy things?
JOE:
Sure.
I'm quite strong,
and I've had the training.
SALLY:
Good.
Now as far as experience goes, they mention they want someone with a licence,
and that you have experience of driving in London –
so you can cope with the traffic and so on.
JOE:
Yes, no problem.
SALLY:
And you've got experience of warehouse work … and the final thing they mention
is customer service.
I think looking at your CV you're OK there.
JOE:
Right.
So what about pay?
Can you tell me a bit more about that, please …